fracture not the fall every scar speaks in a language that we can't recall betrayal
wasn't chaos it was coded design a map of where you trusted a map of every
blind line they smile like allies move like knives in the dark left bleeding
in silence just to study the mark but you didn't disappear you translated the
Play
Loyalty factors under pressure and need
So you study behavior like a strategist who reads
No emotion unchecked, no reaction for free
Every move calculated, every silence a key
You don't chase validation, you withdraw your demand
Now they reach for your presence, they don't understand
But calculated state, unpredictable, rhythm, impossible, read
You become the answer they secretly need
You don't reveal, you imply
You suggest, let them build your power
Inside of their chest
Scarsity sharpens the value you hold
Distance converts attention to gold
Design what you
Look up from another one, a psyche's midnight fright displays
Lovering
like disaster is a farm someone hit the relics in the laundry by the stairs
someone's acting casual while conducting psychic prayers
Forbidden hymns like he dreams
She came in with righteousness, like stolen sunbeams.
Miseric kid, call your ma-
call your man this holy love play the same fake the bird twist the knife and quote a line but all that
thunder from your pope it is just failure with a better shine step one find a target step two
for cry persecution when somebody checks your game step five pass off your
hatred and some higher calling
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I got carried away. No, you're fine. You just did a Michael. You just did a Michael.
Yeah.
Why is Joe Shipley looking at me like that? Joe Shipley is creepy.
Blue eyes and red hair. That has to be like Satan himself. What do you think?
This guy I
Mean
Why does he have his head shape?
It's scary. Okay. Oh, I'm gonna change the background. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. I'm gonna be well. No, don't don't be sorry
I I just saw a video today. It's like it was one of those border videos
where you know
Smuggler got caught and
homeboy had shaved his head just like that, but then pasted a wig on and the
wig had all the drugs in it. That is the best idea. I mean, hey, would you mind
wearing a wig and going to South America for me for just a weekend? I just need you to carry a bag for me down there and then bring a bag back. That's all I need. Is that okay?
You know what I've heard some different stories
I'm not gonna play your games
There's there's plenty of stories the you know pick it pick an old man that's like oh
I I'm just traveling here like I'm just
Hey, I track what you're traveling man track. Are you a Mason?
No, okay
No, I'm just I'm just a me
And uh, you know, I'm trackable. Hey, the quack is in the building. Can I get a quack less quack sound?
Quack back you heard
Crack crack
Who's that Puerto Rican woman yelling in the background? You know, bitch
I'm so sorry, nevermind nevermind. I don't want to I don't I didn't call her bitch. It's a song
It's okay, then you let the Puerto Rican woman back on she's fine
So we're having fun tonight guys. I think I have half an hour left until
Yeah, your page? I heard it, too. Page, are you there? Page, are you there? Is that page?
I heard her, too. I hear her. I hear her. She's, I'm coming home.
And Dragonball, have you, do you know Page had that voice? Have you ever heard her
read that sound? Oh, wait, we have another guest. Who's this? Oh, no. I don't trust this person. I
Hey, I want, I hear a sound.
Good.
Hey, put yourself full scripting.
I will, I will, I'm gonna do it right now.
They're not even like...
Put me full scripting.
I don't care.
They left, they left.
They left.
We fool, we already won.
We already won against those motherfuckers.
Okay?
We already won.
Did you hear how I read the term?
I'm talking about psyche always wins.
Have you heard that term before?
Well
Have you heard pay pretty page always wins have you heard that term pretty page. Are you here pretty page? Are you here?
I think she's backstage, okay? Yeah, go up under I look you make a dolphin sound
One time, I want to hear you. I want to hear you. I want you an LES. Can we get dolphin sound when you guys
Against the sound right here
You make that sound
Well, I can make that sound but
Here can make it right now. I want to hear it right now
Yeah
That's good. Yeah, it's pretty good. L-E-S-T-N-U
Yeah, yeah, no goes you two
Well, the online guys, what is going on? What is what the fuck is that?
What's going on guys? Okay guys, do you want to hear I think I have a song for us. Do you hear a song?
You're down
Yeah, and any business
Okay, how about oh, do you see Casey's modeling days, you know, Casey was a model, you know who KZ is
No, oh, he well, he's a guy with no teeth. He's in jail right now from like assaulting police officers
But here's his modeling days. I have it right here
Yeah, this Casey. Oh shit
Okay, yeah, I have Casey's modeling days. Here he goes. Casey, come on. Come on up
Oh my god, I'm so sorry
From a queen up here, but oh you might as well be up here with two fucking potatoes. These guys don't even talk I
Know
I miss you
Don't I so say some raise your mic. You can't even hear you dick untrackable
You gotta say more than one still able an hour my man. You just call me a potato. Yeah
He's like he's holding a shoulder by himself. He's got you two guys to that potatoes. It's like just that air
of the
Hey guys, check out coldcodex.com, click dot me, coldcodex.me, I've fixed it, a lot of it,
and it's going to be the best. I don't think anybody in the streamer versus me made a better
cold codex than me. I mean, I'm impressed with myself. Elias, are you there?
There's a Puerto Rican woman available. I want to say hello to her.
I heard I heard a I heard a woman screaming
Yeah, can I talk to Veronica or whatever, Victoria Veronica
Okay, I'd have to loop it
I'd have to loop a please
Hello
What is here
Who's yeah, are you the house party LES LES? Why are you at a house party?
Right house party right now
That's Stephen King's voice is Stephen King your house
I know, I know who Stephen King is.
Do you know who Stephen King is?
Yeah, nah.
Oh my Jesus.
Jesus.
Do you want a trackable?
Here, can I have my beers?
Yeah, can I have my beers?
There's all my white claws.
Okay, they're all in the trash.
This is what I have.
It's all good then.
I know everybody. Um I share the love everywhere I go. Have you seen have you seen anything like this in your life?
That's a Big Mac. Do you want to see me take a bite of my Big Mac?
Oh, hey, let me just tell you about Alex
He's scared
Yeah, he's scared and the the reason why he's scared is because
Everyone else is bigger than him. Oh my god
Why is he a dwarf? No, no, no, he just
You can run your mouth
And you but you don't run these streets, you know the thing are you that are you the king of the streets?
No, I'm not a king. No, I am not but but I know my part and I I know my place, you know, I'm saying
And and I'm I'm not bowing down to anybody because honestly
The the host of the show is the king of the moment
Yes, I am
Another song and you ever heard a song and I play one more song. Yeah, go ahead music all night long
Okay, how about this one?
Here we go, it gets up. Where's it up again here?
B
Gather around my faithful crew
I've got a message just for you
Wear your sparkles, bring your wigs
Tonight we're dancing with wild jigs
We're not just followers, we're free
In this funky cultish breed
Raise your hands, let's start the show
In this-
Get up here, Mason, you need to come up right now.
Now, you do it now.
chance and crazy moves in this cold the rhythm grew
Mason, where are you left?
Mason, get back up here!
Mason, where'd you go?
Hold on, take it down.
Mason, what happened?
Mason, where'd you go?
Oh, who's this?
I don't see anybody there.
Mason, where are you?
I missed you.
Bro, bro.
They said you miss me miss me to use it. They said you miss me
And some more Big Mac
Hey, I try to reject Big Mac's I
Call it food called food. Yeah
We're Mason go
My amazing come over here and then you left
Well, who's the first message?
Sure
You make clip, huh
Okay, this one is burning burning you predator clips, I don't I mean, I don't even know what to say
but
I don't feel like playing a little my show right now
Anyway, thanks a lot for that. I see him. I saw him. I saw him. I saw him.
Jack, would you like the picture of me?
I do like it. Yeah
It looks like it looks at me a lot. Hey, it's it's a bit extreme
Do I look like a monster?
No, it's not a
It's not a hey, this is what you look like. Oh, I mean it is have you seen this one? This one
What what do they call it a a caricature? You see that one a
Caricature, have you ever heard that is a caricature?
I don't know my feelings that hurt your
Why did it hurt your feelings? I'm covered on the green vomit and my eyes are bolting out of my head
Well, you know, um, I like some of his I like some of his work. I don't like that one
Why am I covered in green vomit? I wouldn't know that
Hey
Artists do what they do
I don't know if he's an artist though, he's like some gay black or not black, but he's a gay Mexican or whatever. I don't know
But again
You know so much of what it is is the words
typed into AI like
I want to make can I make a video of you on track? What a drag will get on the screen real quick
I'm gonna make a video. I'm gonna make a view you don't mind you sit on screen
I'll do it. Okay. Okay. There you are on screen. I'm gonna put a full screen and I'm gonna take a picture real quick
Once again, okay, print screen. Oh, shit
They oh, I got it. I got it. I don't think oh shit. I want
cancel
Yeah
Once I got no, I'm not worried about it
And then you're not and I here we go. Okay. Yeah, but where am I what why can I get out of this picture?
Okay, I'm gonna do a pretty screen of this one
Print screen, okay, selection.
Okay, I got it, I got you, okay.
There we go, I got it, okay, I got it.
How do I close this out?
I'm gonna take myself off for a second.
I don't know why I can't give myself out for this.
Okay, cancel.
Okay, got it, got it.
Okay, I'm back, okay, I'm back.
Was that intractable?
Okay, I'm gonna take your view.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Are you sure you're ready for this?
Yeah, for sure. Okay. I'm gonna say turn. Okay. Well
Add the media. Let me see desktop
Got it got it. Okay, got you
Okay, oh
Excuse me
I'm actually
I'm actually intrigued like
You got me on edge right now. I was like, I can't wait. I can't wait
You can't wait. Okay. It's coming up. I'm making it right now. I
Can do this really quickly except magician. Okay. Are you ready for yourself?
You're ready to see yourself
send it
Yeah
Really ready here you go
Desktop here you are downloads it's in down here. How's this? How do you like this?
My goodness, you gave me good teeth. I
That you you're mad
That's you. Oh
Bro, that is beautiful
I wasn't missing this shit
Hey, I zoomed in and you didn't even catch the gold in my mouth. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I missed that part, but I did my best I couldn't.
Oh, no, you got off lucky. You know what I thought you were doing, Ronys?
I thought he came up and turned to the side and you were gonna make a picture of him and like you and Shibby kissing.
That's what I thought we were about to watch.
I think it's next level.
After all, potatoes on track. Well, you got off lucky, bro.
That's level
Hey, how about this Alex? I've done more than you'll ever do. I
Know you have my man. You're in the army, man. You were cooked you cook potatoes now
You are a potato you became a potato you became what you cooked. Isn't that funny?
No, fuck that
We're talking about we're talking about
Man in a garage does not paint it next to a fucking mountain of cans of course light
Nah, bro, we're talking a potato and he sounds like you or from Winnie the Pooh. That's what we're talking about
We're talking about in a person
This will read dick. What's that? He already I scary. That's yeah, and you
Can make fun of my face all day long
Something you're ever gonna do because you're scared
Yeah, don't be scared of my face. You're scared
Thank you, pal, thank you
Yo, you know what I want these losers alive the losers alive, right? They're all over the chicken woman, you know, I am I
Want to hunt them down?
Hey guys, how about we go over there and yeah, let's read them. Yes, cuz they allow you there. That's right
No, I wish no money money's live with the loser
Is he I'll read Sam in what's up Papa's I have another picture that before I go before I go
I have another picture of untrackable
you ready for a trackable are you ready?
you asked for it on trackable scene
oh you wanted this picture right?
you wanted it?
you asked for it and now you're gonna get it pal
assumed it
ahh look at it on trackable
all crazy and hairy
and we're firing
a joker's here someone posted a link
love joker
like that on trackable that's you
The trackable that was untrackable. Fuck that's him now. Actually, let's show me when I met him
The show transformation. Yeah. No, no, that's the middle. That was a year ago
That's now and go back to his photo when I first met him. We can see the whole transformation my man the whole process
YouTube did to untrackable when I met him he was a young handsome fellow
Well
Look at you now
Yeah
There you go. No, there you go. There you go a year into YouTube and boom three years later. There you go
That's the intractable timeline and that's how it goes my pips up here
Hey, I'm gonna, I'm gonna mom
If I could say um, you know
Judging appearance. No Ronis. You're good man. You're good because you get it, you know, you can like
You get the joke and you can adapt and react man. You're good. You should be a house turn or some shit
It takes short people like that
But you know people could just pull that off you know and caught it like I was no a timeline boom boom picture picture
And I had a fourth picture now. This is the fourth. There's a fourth one
Eventually here's your to know this. I mean we all share image file downloads. Yeah, I think this is him
Hold on. I didn't get it yet. Okay. I need to go back to
Okay, I'll find it later. But yeah, he turned even scarier. Oh my god. That's gold bro. The untrackable timeline
You know, we got a clip and chip that
Before and after bro and everything in between
Yeah, and that's what I'm saying is like, you know
You know, I get the
The you don't get nothing. You don't even even know I do come on bro
Hey, how about you get this?
How about you make something fun? How about you make something funny?
like
Knock knock knock knock
To knock up joke they go with me knock knock and I have the fourth image and at the fifth knock knock
You can make me look like the most scariest thing this bearded monster this fang day asshole
All these things are crackable knock knock
Who's there?
Hatch
Hatch who?
God bless you
I mean one more now. Here's another one and I have one more
Hi, and then here's a final transformation
To all motherfucking Alexander got me having allergies and shit
Yeah, you look you had a little reaction to something but you're so cute. I would still do you I would
Oh, that's the fourth one. That's what you're headed on track. Oh, that's next year 20 27
No, let's go from the beginning. Let's start from the beginning. This was 20 22 when I met him
This is 20 24
20 20 no, we skipped a couple. That's 20 28. Yeah, that this is 20 26
You know, he can't leave and that's 2028 and then oh and I
I'm gonna be dirty that yeah, there you go. I mean, I'm honestly
on a decade on YouTube
Hey, hey, I'm trying to figure out how y'all fixed my teeth
and gave me
Because I got I got get I got gap teeth in the front. I don't have any fangs
But you fixed my gap and gave me fangs
Literally like you guys
I got a drop and monitor. Let's see what's going on down there
Like
It was pretty good though pretty good pretty good. You gotta say those were those are beautiful pictures
But I I've never seen myself as some sort of monster and I've never
Imagined someone in silky your wife or your kids or something that that's what you turn into you turn to like this attack beast, right?
I mean
Maybe maybe maybe not okay. Maybe we're done
Well, I do think you're cute, but I'm sorry. I don't want to insult your wife or anything. Hey, you're cute. I'm sorry. I
like your voice
But
Mmm-hmm. Oh, he's mad. He's mad. I got him mad. I got finally got a mad finally
Go ahead. Go ahead. At least you're unless you're anger. Oh, here. Here. Hey. Have you seen my cat Lenore?
The there was a time there was a time and a place for everything
I'm Jackable. I like you. You're cute. I'm Lenore. I'm a female. I like you, Jackable.
I'm sorry. I don't like black cats. Fuck you, bitch.
Or why do you say that? Look at Lenore. She's not just mad.
I'm so sorry. It's okay. I'm so sorry.
Go to a comedy club sometime and you'll realize just how unimportant you are.
Attractable! You're a fucking nigger! On the door! Bad! Bad!
Oh my god. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I didn't say it. I didn't say it.
I don't know why she's like that sometimes. I'm so sorry. I didn't know she was gonna say the word.
Nor
It's quite a break. It's okay. It's okay. Wow. I'm sorry guys. Wow. I'm really sorry about that
Nor yeah one
Once you hear explosions
Words don't really matter too much anymore
right
Right, but I don't like the norse in the n-word. It's like it's not it's not becoming a black cat to see
Are you wanna, Ilya? Ilya, show me your butthole again.
I'll call you at N-word, I will.
And Lenore can say it, she's black.
I can't say it, because I'm too white to say it.
Lenore has a lot to say it.
Andraga, would you ever see me eat a Big Mac on stream?
Andraga?
Allowed.
Who allows anybody to do anything?
or is it more about somebody to, you know, stop you?
No, that's not me.
Yeah, again, nobody's going to stop you,
but, you know, they may come after you in the,
what do you call it, the-
The panel verse?
No, the,
Because there's there's a pre and then there's a current and then there's an after
It's like
You know
It's all over your chest that way
Oh, yeah, I think gave you come all over your chest, but this is your own
Okay
You come over yourself
No, I
Agree, I agree. I don't think it's gay
Yeah, and then it's called a psyche first. It's called a psyche first. No, we got we got a
Exclusive untrackable. It's not gay if you come over to hey untrackable if you can stuff your own dick, would you have your own dick? Oh?
For sure I would okay. Is that gay? I
Would never leave the fucking house
Got you this is a real man
This is actually a real man giving real man stuff like every every gay guy says oh, no
I would never suck my own dick. I'm trackable is a straight man with it. He's married
And he would do it. He admits he I like how honest he is. I believe
You talk about only fans
Do you have one? I
Would have begging people
To be like hey, I want to see this dude suck his own dick and like I would tease him
Like hey, I
Stick my tongue out
That cost you five dollars
You know this this whole thing has it's gone down before like
Ron Jeremy is in prison for the rest of his life, or the things that he has done behind the scenes in his profession.
He is?
But he was literally offered a million dollars to do a gay thing.
Yeah, I'm I'm sure he made plenty of money doing whatever
Jeremy my man. He lived on the block for me. Okay, and he fought for a tree
Because they the city of New York he lived on the block for me that bad ugly fuck all these men
I was seeing giant cock now bless the man
Don't know how that happened that that shows you that women don't give a fuck about looks basically
You know if you can fuck that thing that that's not that but the fat fuck lived on the block for me
City New York was like we're gonna cut down this tree for some reason and he like tied himself to the tree
It was like a thing before he got arrested. So he he was the world's biggest porn star
Lived in Queens for a tree got arrested for rape
How's that for a Netflix special pal?
You gotta rate people your job was fucking 24 seven for 30 years
You still haven't urged like you didn't fucking up for like what?
That's scary shit
See his mind is conditioned by now and he's so ugly and it was over. This is my theory
Because there's no way you're going to read someone after all you did was fuck for 90 years
So my theory is this guy once he lost the golden touch
He still needed that power and that right and then once the girls are like no ill like
He had to go there and that's why that pig is behind bars
Am I good? Am I good?
And not so much different is like
You got Alexander in ypd. It's like
The power was New York police department my man. What's your mouth my boy?
the job wasn't enough like I had to impose myself and be like hey you can't
stand here you can't do this you can I never I never was anyone big I rock
drug dealers I punch some fucking dick in handcuffs I PD I was
Where I go, you son of a potato boy
You got it all wrong potato man, I'll lock you up in a heart
All these weird people you all get the one Kate went on on money
Get the move we got oh
We're getting poor bombs a king of poor. Oh, no, that's yoga
Oh
He's one of my favorite
He's number two. It's like he and then joke up. Can we see the old black mountain shit the broke back mountain intro?
Just to get everyone acquainted with Joker and Ronis
Watch Alexander McQueen in the prison showers
Please you got video of that. I didn't see that video. It's like so I figured out like how it's really song requests on
Stream it's if you have to use nightbot. Yeah, it's SR that SR one, right?
Yeah, yeah
Trackable with his little pussy sponge
And I also if you know how to do speech to speech chat so like it's text to speech when people type it's speech chat calm
Yeah, thank you for that. You want to try it?
I'm gonna try it. Actually, I've been doing the song request Joker 2 like now and it's like it's really
Big helps me, but I do think I have oh, hey, I do have something to show you guys
You know Joker and I spent some time alone in a in a beautiful place
We spent some time in a hopeless place. It was beautiful place actually called broke yag mountain and Joker
I went to broke yag mountain together and then here here. We are you watch you went to broke your ass Mountain
If you're looking for work, I suggest you get in here.
Oh my god, this brings me out of a depression.
But this will save me.
Well, since you're going to be working together.
Rick, it's time we start drinking yet.
What is this? What is this? My pussy?
Woo-hoo!
Do you know somebody named Jack?
He was fishing buddies.
Can we take my shirt off?
You know, it could be like this, just like this always.
This thing grabs hold of us in the wrong place, and we're dead.
Boris, you're found a way to make the 10th pass the deer.
You don't go up there if you don't want to.
He's done the nipples.
But the psyche is mine, I've never seen psyche so happy in my fucking life.
I like good actually
Actually good
That was the best that those are the best sides of my life. I think that was the best
Wow, Joe, I like it. Honestly, not good next thing
Here you go. Hey, do you want to say how do we all talking about you?
We're talking about all kinds of fun shit. Hi Joker. You're when is the drama gonna begin?
Joker is a nigger. Hey Lenore
No
So I'm saying the n-word. She's black so she's allowed to say it, but she called you the n-word. I'm sorry
Oh, no, I hope the I hope your arch-nemesis didn't hear that. I
Don't think I don't think they did hey, but Joker look how cute you are this guy
you can cut it off
and you keep throwing the n-word in there like here and there like sneakily like what's that about
is that to like ensure you erase the panel later like is that a safety mechanism like i hear it
while it's under mayors and i aren't a campaign to bring back the n-word
if you are
really
yeah
You know it's against TOS
It's okay
It's okay. No, not for Google. It's not
Google on YouTube. I'm gonna delete that. I'm gonna leave this your map towards it doesn't matter anyway. All right
Have a good night
I'm sorry, Lenore call. Oh, I'm sorry. Oh
I'm sorry Lenore college that word
I'm sorry, Lenore bad cat bad bad bad
Dragonball, it's just you and me.
Are you- is it too gay?
Yeah.
If you know, you know, nigga.
Oh my God.
You said the N word on my show.
Okay, Dragonball, let's watch a video together.
Let's watch a video.
Will you watch a video with me?
Yeah, I'm down.
Okay, let's watch it.
Let's watch one video.
How about this one?
Oh my God, that's not, that's not it.
Okay.
à¤
à¤¦à¥à¤¯à¤¾à¤à¤à¥à¤°à¤¾
à¤ªà¤°à¤¾ à¤®à¥à¤¶à¥à¤µà¤°à¥ à¤¶à¥à¤¦à¥à¤§à¥ à¤¶à¤à¥à¤¤à¥
i just don't try to i don't see them dance ever ever ever
When you crack up or when you're fucking dancin', bro.
Oh my god, look at that.
We're at a dance party.
You like that, Alex?
Hello?
Harold?
A car?
It hurts.
That was that was a good song. Thank you. That was in that was in San Francisco. I never seen you shake that shit
Unjuggable so I got clipped and chipped
Here you go
Hey, you didn't like my finger dance
Not at all. It looked like you were doing the fucky thing when you do the circle and put your finger through it
It wasn't cool
Your girl like my finger dance
Yo, are you talking about my girl, bro
You want some beef?
Why wouldn't I talking about my my biatch
You think you can you think you can keep me down
What the fuck does that mean? Is that a gay terminology? I'm not keeping nothing down.
Just one punch to the jaw by your brain rattles, your knees buckle.
Doesn't matter how big you are. You catch that motherfucker in the jaw with your heart is fucking
right hook, later pal. Or an uppercut, that'll work too.
So how are we gonna be bros if you're against my dick?
Once again, gay.
No, I know what I'm sorry, bro, but you don't got to go full gator night dick
It's a meeting gay
Is it against gay or
Or you know, you just told me how you want my dick pressed against you like you're getting gay now
No, but you've got nothing to protect
You feel me protect your neck. I gotta protect my neck
You wish
You wish I wish upon a star. That's what I wish
Twinkle twinkle little star
What I wonder what you are
The only thing I
Protect your neck against is bobbin on my cock
You can't bob on a cock
Protecting your neck like the math doesn't make sense there, bro. It's not like bobbing apples bobbing a con
well
of all that can be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to be sold to
i'm i'm i'm automatically jewish because i gotta you don't say those words up here we say
it starts with j and rhymes with us okay we don't say though just like the f word you gotta spell
So, so you're a loser, but if I put an L in front of it, you know what I think that might be the first
More thing you said in the past three years. Oh
Shit
What rhymes with who's that and starts with an Looza
Yo, my main just killed it yo
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, God, that's cool.
I was going to work on.
I'm going to find I'm going to find one that rhymes with Hispanic.
English Manic, I don't know.
That's going to be a hard one.
Yeah, it's going to be.
You guys make it so easy, but you guys make it so hard.
Resistance you need it
Imagine everything was easy that would suck you need to fight through resistance the more resistance the better bro
That's what makes you good resistance. You cannot become something without resistance, bro
Where's my little be the leader
Is that Peter no, that's my friend my marcia my Russian friend. Oh
That's thing that is no with something
Look at the cat me out of the purring the cat that cat loves her
Take a moment he's wasn't you I think I think it was you could have sworn
Long time ago. You had a video you at your friend's house like a neighbor like this is my neighbor and it was two hot girls
Yeah, am I meaning or did I see that right?
I went to my neighbor's house there. What are my neighbors were here and there's like these beautiful women? Yeah
Yeah, they moved away. She moved away, but yeah, they were they were hot. Yeah
I just I just I just be beautiful people. I don't know what to say
You're attracting all what you are you're a magnet to what you think and
Birds of a feather flock together. You don't see peregrine falcons flying with pigeons
That you'll never see that
Pigeons fly with pigeons falcons fly with falcons
Mason says that I bring the cheese sticks psyche because if not we can't be cool with each other anymore the cheese sticks
What Mason, what are you saying? Oh, I'm eating a call. Oh, yeah
Suspected spam caller
I don't know that was hey, you know Alex, you know, I got like a bunch of groceries sent to my house today Alex
Was that the person we banned Chantay and whatever Perkins because they were trying to like take credit for that
no, that wasn't it wasn't she didn't send the groceries, but I don't know the person wants me to say who it was
But someone sent me groceries
They said I mean if they don't mind that we would love to know who the hell it was
They can tell themselves if they want to but I'll just say that they sent me a bunch of
Groceries and a white claw and thank you so much because that was so cool
And they got they knew I had an air fryer, so they got all air fires. I already ate the whole box of shrimp
this whole box of shrimp they sent. I ate that whole box of shrimp. I'm cooking that shrimp.
You're just making a joke with these. Okay. Mason, come on here. I can see that. How do you make
one shirt? Wonder. Get up here, Mason. Is it a one shirt? That's amazing. When you get what you get,
you get it, how you get it, where it comes from. You don't care.
because you know I've gotten a lot and I don't care where it comes from just
hey food move move
it's amazing bro how long we've been alive and we have to eat three times a
day minimum you know the we've had food all our lives like does anyone think
about that but that's incredible wherever it comes from like you're saying
That just the fact that we have we eat like imagine no food you die. Have you ever been hungry?
We've been living fucking 90 years still food food food food. That's a blessing
And Alex, Alex, you've seen me food and like, and somebody else has sent me food and so
it's like, I mean, literally, you're keeping me alive, you guys are keeping me alive actually.
And it's like, people will say, Oh, don't send them anything, don't send them, like,
I would literally starve sometimes if I, if I need some help, and so I appreciate it so
much.
And it's like, yeah.
Right.
I understand this, but what he's saying about three times a day, um,
You need breakfast by lunchtime. You're hungry again by nighttime. You're hungry again. I mean, that's like the norm
Yeah, I mean some people eat more and the ones that eat less like it sucks to go through the day with like one meal
You know the body
No, unless you're a fucking Marine in the jungle like I don't gotta eat for 72 hours like that's different, bro
Oh, hey, that is life for a lot of people
No shit. That's my point. How lucky we are
solid
Even out here in the real world one meal
Every three days
It's like if you get solid calories every three days
It's like hey
He's not getting a drone eats, but you know
Food when I'm really hungry and I really appreciate people's enemy
That's all I was trying to say is that thank you for everyone that sends me food because I'll eat everything
I'll eat on camera if you want me to eat on camera. I just appreciate it because you're keeping me alive basically
I'm not even talking about you. I was talking about the planet
You weren't even my mind about hunger. Honestly
I'm just talking about how lucky us three are that we have been alive for 40 plus years
and we have food every day some way somehow right whether we work for it or we get it
like whatever that's a blessing that's a miracle bro to go through like you know hunger bro like
you know how cheesy i mean we missed a meal here and there and you feel that hunger that's
I think I might end soon, but I'm gonna show,
I'm gonna find a show for us all to go to.
And it's either you can go troll there
or you can be a real person, let me see.
I think maybe, what should I send to everybody?
Oh, maybe another guest, actually.
What
Why quacks the man yo Alex. I want your Alex. I want to show you something hold up. Talk to me
Yo, look at this. I know I told that
Turned in BTB that's turned in BTB
You know his laugh his laugh is crazy
That's turning B2B making up
Well, it makes them happy Ronis, you know you just whatever it makes them happy
Yeah, exactly. If he's going to be happy and me throwing him in the bushes, it makes you guys happy, man. I'm all on board.
Yo, I got something else. I didn't put up yet, but I might show you now and you tell me if it's fucked up or not.
Yo, niggas stay out of my life.
But you can't go up and hijack Psychic's panel with this shit.
he was just about to end it and show us something and now you've got these things
oh no he's about to oh he's about to end and end it
it's alive right i'll go to you and we'll fucking make money he goes all night go start a life
so i think i'm gonna end it so it's either you or money for 20 and i definitely don't want to go there
it's called the saman second channel called he has another channel i don't know what it's called though
Mm-hmm. What channel? What channel? We tell them all Sam and his second channel for what it's called
It's called. Oh, oh, he's got a backup channel now. He's he finally got on board
With the back of
No, he's always had that he plays video games on me
No, but not as a good kid like he plays video games
He's got a backup channel. He plays video games. We find out. Oh, you can like that. You can't be that bad
Oh, if you play video games like kind of thing
You can be spending your time doing a lot of shit
He's not live nobody's live. I don't think I see money for 20 and less. It's about to be
Okay, well, why don't we go to money for 20 is that I was gonna money's let's go to money's all of us
Let me up. He's not let me up
I'll make him make play you up. No, he's gonna know he's running his panel with Christian. I saw that
Fuck that. I won't make you up. Take don't worry. Let's go. There's a link guys
There's a link and everyone go over there
I'm gonna like to get a little nap and I'll be back tonight after midnight probably
You're the best. I love you guys. Thank you so much and there's there's money for 20s channel
Let's go over there. See you've been ready by psyche. I love you guys. See you soon